So we modified the file and mode parameters as mentioned in the zipfile documentation.
حسنًا، عدّلنا معلمات الملف والوضع كما هو مذكور في وثائق zipfile.
File and mode.
الملف والوضع.
So, our file is called,
بالتالي، يتم استدعاء الملف
online-job-postings.zip, and the mode we want is read,
online-job-postings.zip وتتم قراءة الوضع الذي نريده،
r, not w, write.
r وليس w write.
Then we can process the cell using shift and enter. What happened here?
وبعد ذلك يمكننا معالجة الخلية بالضغط على shift وenter. إذن ماذا حدث هنا؟
We have zipfile not defined.
لدينا zipfile غسر مُعرف.
Okay. That's what we have to do.
حسنًا. هذا ما يتعين علينا القيام به.
With zipfile.zipfile.
من خلال zipfile.zipfile.
And that should do it.
وهذا سيفي بالغرض.
Let's check our folder in our terminal to see if our file was extracted from the zipfile.
دعونا نتحقق من مجلدنا في جهازنا لمعرفة ما إذا كان الملف الخاص بك قد تم استخراجه من zipfile.
And we'll type ls.
وسنقوم بكتابة ls.
And it looks like it is. Data job posts.csv.
ويبدو الأمر كذلك. بيانات طلبات وظائف csv.
We actually check it here too.
نتحقق من ذلك هنا أيضًا.
And there it is as well.
وهناك أيضًا.
Great job.
عمل جيد.
We now have ourselves a csv file.
لدينا الآن ملف csv.
We'll cover this file type in the next video.
وسنعمل على تغطية نوع الملف هذا في الفيديو التالي.
Plus the actual exciting part of gathering,
بالإضافة إلى الجزء الممتع الفعلي للتجميع،
which is opening, or importing the data set in our programming environment.
الذي يفتح أو يستورد مجموعة البيانات في بيئة البرمجة الخاصة بنا.